labtestsonline.org 2017-06-21

# Policies

AACC is committed to honoring the privacy of our visitors. We have designed the Website to minimize the gathering of personal data, and we do not collect any personally-identifying data unless you voluntarily provide it or authorize us or our partners to collect it.

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes our policies with respect to information that AACC collects through the website at www.labtestsonline.org ("Website").

By visiting the Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Policy.

_Privacy Policy Support_  
If you have an inquiry or concern about our Policy, please contact Dominique Smith at [dsmith@aacc.org](mailto:dsmith@aacc.org).

_Changes in this Policy_  
AACC may amend this Policy at any time without notice. Your use of the Website after changes to this Policy means that you are accepting such changes. Please visit our Website to obtain current information about our Policy.

_Information Collected_  
The information we collect generally includes: (1) Personal information you supply and (2) Tracking information collected as you navigate through the Website.

_Personally Identifiable Information_  
We may collect and store personally identifiable information whenever you contact us with a question or comment. If you contact our customer service, we may ask you to provide certain personal information like your name, mailing address, telephone number, mobile number, and/or email address.

_Aggregate Information_  
AACC does collect non-personal data to help us understand how the Website is being used – and how we can improve it. Our web server log also collects certain non-personal information such as the domain you are using to surf the web (e.g., users of your ISP will show up as "ISPname.com") and the page from which you linked to our site, if indeed you followed a link from elsewhere on the web.

When we collect this information, we endeavor to make any personally identifiable information non-personally identifiable by combining it with information about other individuals or by removing characteristics that make the information personally identifiable to you. AACC reserves the right to share with third parties aggregated information about you and other visitors to our Website.

AACC uses a third-party advertising company, eHealthcare Solutions (EHS), to serve ads when you visit the Website. EHS uses cookies to serve ads on the Website. The use of cookies enables EHS to serve more relevant ads to our users based on visits to the Website and other sites on the Internet. EHS may use non-identifying information about your visits to the Website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out of having this information used by EHS, see their [Preference Manager](http://preferences.truste.com/2.0/?type=ehs&affiliateId=151). You may also review eHealthcare Solutions' [Privacy Policy](http://ehealthcaresolutions.com/Privacy).

_Storing and Using Information_  
We do not undertake to maintain any information about you for a duration greater than necessary to provide services to you or as provided by law, rule or regulation. The Lab Tests Online website invites users to submit personally-identifiable data, such as your name and email address, along with questions or comments about the site, or about your experiences in the healthcare system. We collect this data only so that we may contact you with a response to your questions or comments, or to follow up with questions of our own. If you have indicated that you are interested in receiving updates about the site, we will use your email address to send you an email noting such updates. The Website is not governed by HIPAA or any other patient privacy statute.

_Sharing Information_  
AACC is not in the business of renting or selling information to others. We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include providing customer service, performing business analysis, and supporting our Website functionality, other features offered through our Website. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not authorized to share or use such information for any other purposes.

We may also transfer user or customer information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale.

We may disclose specific information in response to a valid court order, subpoena, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law, to enforce our Website policies, or to protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful. We may share information to prevent illegal uses of the Website, or defend ourselves against third-party claims. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

_Opt Out or Change Information_  
If you do not want to receive email from us, or you want to prevent your information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected, please let us know by sending an email to Dominique Smith at [dsmith@aacc.org](mailto:dsmith@aacc.org). Due to production, mailing, and system timelines, it may take some time to process your request. In addition, we may still use your information to communicate with you for other purposes, such as for customer service.

_Children_  
We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from persons under the age of 18. We do not have a mechanism for determining the age of the visitors to our Website.

_International Users_  
This Website is operated, in whole or in part, from the United States. By using this Website, regardless of where you live in the world, you consent to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States, and allow AACC to use and collect your personal information in accordance with this Policy.

_Third Party Links_  
The Website may also contain links to other third party websites that are not under our control. These websites may have their own policies or no policies at all, regarding privacy. You should seek and review these policies before providing information to these websites. AACC has no responsibility for linked websites and provides these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. AACC also maintains a strict "no-spam" policy and fully complies with CAN-SPAM Act regulations.

_Google Analytics_  
Currently we are using Google Analytics to analyze the audience of the website and improve our content. No personal information is collected from Google Analytics. For further information on the privacy policy concerning Google Analytics, please [go here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en).
